Fowler C. West papers, Inclusive: 1964-2009, Bulk: 1965-1993
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), 1975-1993; 2
  - Subjects, 1982-1991; 11
    - Membership Card, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, 1973 CSC Board, 1972 September 20 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, Election Night, 1973 September 25 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Transactions Tax, Futures Contract, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Transnor Ltd. v. BP North America Petroleum, et. al, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Treasury Report, Intermarket Coordination, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - US Treasury Securities Structure, Risk, Regulation, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Volatility of Stock and Derivative Markets, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Volume Investors Corporation, Information, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Volume Investors Corporation, Default, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Working Group on Financial Markets, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Personal, 1964-2005; 3
  Personal materials consist of items relating to Baylor University, biographical information, West’s promotions, invitations, and programs.
  - General, 1964-2005; 1
    - Biographical Information, 1965-1978 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - “Mystery Tour,” Newsweek [Poage to Timbuktu], 1964 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Transfer to Poage’s Congressional Office, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Promotion, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Promotion, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration, Jimmy Carter, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - “In an Old House in Bosqueville”, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Inauguration, Ronald Reagan, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Resume, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Inaugurations, Raymond Mabus [Mississippi Governor], 1988 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - 44th Annual Roll Call Congressional Baseball Game Program, 2005 June 23 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - “Boll Weevil” Pin, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Baylor University, 1982-1983; 2
    - Pi Sigma Alpha, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - “Baylor Line”, 1983 February (Box 66, Folder 7)